1

Email 

Password 

Remember me

    Support & Help
    --------------

    About
    -----

    [Silver10Docs per Month1UserLimited to R 20,000  
    turnover pmR 99](https://www.invoicesonline.co.za/pricing)

    [View Full Pricing Details](https://www.invoicesonline.co.za/pricing)  [Sign Up Now  
    It's free and takes just 30 seconds](https://www.invoicesonline.co.za/your-businesses/add-business)

    ---------------------------------------------------

    -------------------------------------------------------

    Control
    -------

    Manage
    ------

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is important to us. It is Invoices Online PTY (Ltd)'s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, [https://www.invoicesonline.co.za](https://www.invoicesonline.co.za/), and other sites we own and operate.

We will do all that is reasonable to ensure your personal information is kept secure and up to date. However we are unable to guarantee that your personal information will be 100% secure, we have never had a breach & strive to use up to date software & technologies to keep it that way.

We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used. 

Businesses using our system for their business management may add information about their clients.  This information is only available to them.

Our personnel will have access to basic business information in order to provide support - business name, account type, & contact information is made available.  No other information is available to our support personnel.

Business users are automatically subscribed to our newsletter - we do not send it out frequently, only when important changes or new features need to be announced.  We can unsubscribe each individual user on request.

Businesses have full control over the client information they add - they are responsible for ensuring popi compliance with that data.  As soon as an export is downloaded or emailed, we no longer have any control over that data.

We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with non integrated third-parties, except when required by law.  Certain data may be shared with integrated payment gateways (like Ozow, PayFast, PayGate, Netcash, SnapScan, VCS, Zapper) when you make a payment through our system.  Data may also be shared with integrated accounting systems like Xero or Sage One, this is determined by wether the business is integrated with any of those platforms.

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.

You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.

We use Google Analytics to analyze visitor patterns on our system.  Our system does not, and will never contain any advertisements.

Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.

This policy is effective as of 29 June 2021.

More than 1,000 businesses operate more efficiently with us.
============================================================

> Impossible to run our businesses without IO
> -------------------------------------------
> 
> IO is an integral part of our day to day business. It allows me complete control and overview functionality, while still enabling franchise owners to run their various franchises without interruption.  
>   
> At Storietyd.co.za - a bookclub for Afrikaans children, with thousands of members - all our billing is automated, automated invoices, automated debit orders, automated payment allocation, and so forth. Administration would be an absolute nightmare without IO.  
>   
> We are suppliers of bulk educational products to schools, our reps in the field use IO for quotes, invoicing and managing debtors, directly from their smartphones / tablets.  
>   
> We are extremely satisfied with Invoices Online, and would certainly recommend that you try it out.

Kobus Venter

Karino Merinos ( PTY ) LTD

SA Security Brokerz (Pty) Ltd

INDUSTRIAL DRUM SERVICES (PTY)LTD

Konsortium Operations ( Roamfree Meats )

Wiselink Broadband Vryheid

CBR Verwe/Paints

UMVIKELI PRIVATE SECURITY

OPTIMUS ELECTRICAL PTY (LTD)

Skinz Printing & Branding

Qothiphango Mining

De light Investments(Pty)Ltd trading as Serene Memorials

Laurinda Pretorius Spraak en Drama Ateljee

Sarabi

MONSTER SECURITY SERVICES (THABAZIMBI/NORTHAM)

IEMS (PTY) ltd

Some Stats, we are growing rapidly
----------------------------------

* Over **1,000** active businesses
* Over **300,000** clients
* Over **1,000,000** invoices
* Over **30,000** job cards
* Over **100,000** quotes
* Over **R 10,000,000,000** invoiced
* Over **R 10,000,000,000** in payments received

All content copyright © [Invoices Online](https://www.invoicesonline.co.za/) 2024.  
A product of Invoices Online PTY (Ltd)  
15 Howard Street  
Dan Pienaar  
Bloemfontein  
9301
